{
	"nacional": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"65": 3193,
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 anos y mas*",
			"Respuesta": "total",
			"Total": 42326,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"5a11": 5988,
			"p5a11": 14.1,
			"12a25": 11546,
			"p12a25": 27.3,
			"26a40": 10293,
			"p26a40": 24.3,
			"41a64": 11305,
			"p41a64": 26.7,
			"p65": 7.5
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"65": 2426,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 34715,
				"pTotal": 82,
				"5a11": 4627,
				"p5a11": 77.3,
				"12a25": 9903,
				"p12a25": 85.8,
				"26a40": 8472,
				"p26a40": 82.3,
				"41a64": 9287,
				"p41a64": 82.2,
				"p65": 76
			},
			{
				"65": 767,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 7611,
				"pTotal": 18,
				"5a11": 1361,
				"p5a11": 22.7,
				"12a25": 1644,
				"p12a25": 14.2,
				"26a40": 1822,
				"p26a40": 17.7,
				"41a64": 2018,
				"p41a64": 17.8,
				"p65": 24
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"65": 799,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 29794,
				"pTotal": 70.4,
				"5a11": 2435,
				"p5a11": 40.7,
				"12a25": 10503,
				"p12a25": 91,
				"26a40": 8965,
				"p26a40": 87.1,
				"41a64": 7092,
				"p41a64": 62.7,
				"p65": 25
			},
			{
				"65": 2394,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 12533,
				"pTotal": 29.6,
				"5a11": 3553,
				"p5a11": 59.3,
				"12a25": 1043,
				"p12a25": 9,
				"26a40": 1328,
				"p26a40": 12.9,
				"41a64": 4214,
				"p41a64": 37.3,
				"p65": 75
			}
		]
	},
	"cabeceras": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"65": 2616,
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 anos y mas*",
			"Respuesta": "total",
			"Total": 33456,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"5a11": 4423,
			"p5a11": 13.2,
			"12a25": 8867,
			"p12a25": 26.5,
			"26a40": 8328,
			"p26a40": 24.9,
			"41a64": 9222,
			"p41a64": 27.6,
			"p65": 7.8
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"65": 2012,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 27968,
				"pTotal": 83.6,
				"5a11": 3499,
				"p5a11": 79.1,
				"12a25": 7770,
				"p12a25": 87.6,
				"26a40": 6979,
				"p26a40": 83.8,
				"41a64": 7708,
				"p41a64": 83.6,
				"p65": 76.9
			},
			{
				"65": 604,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 5488,
				"pTotal": 16.4,
				"5a11": 924,
				"p5a11": 20.9,
				"12a25": 1097,
				"p12a25": 12.4,
				"26a40": 1349,
				"p26a40": 16.2,
				"41a64": 1514,
				"p41a64": 16.4,
				"p65": 23.1
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"65": 737,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 24996,
				"pTotal": 74.7,
				"5a11": 1920,
				"p5a11": 43.4,
				"12a25": 8364,
				"p12a25": 94.3,
				"26a40": 7635,
				"p26a40": 91.7,
				"41a64": 6339,
				"p41a64": 68.7,
				"p65": 28.2
			},
			{
				"65": 1879,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 8460,
				"pTotal": 25.3,
				"5a11": 2503,
				"p5a11": 56.6,
				"12a25": 503,
				"p12a25": 5.7,
				"26a40": 692,
				"p26a40": 8.3,
				"41a64": 2883,
				"p41a64": 31.3,
				"p65": 71.8
			}
		]
	},
	"centrosPoblados": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"65": 577,
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 anos y mas*",
			"Respuesta": "total",
			"Total": 8870,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"5a11": 1565,
			"p5a11": 17.6,
			"12a25": 2679,
			"p12a25": 30.2,
			"26a40": 1965,
			"p26a40": 22.2,
			"41a64": 2083,
			"p41a64": 23.5,
			"p65": 6.5
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"65": 414,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 6747,
				"pTotal": 76.1,
				"5a11": 1128,
				"p5a11": 72.1,
				"12a25": 2132,
				"p12a25": 79.6,
				"26a40": 1493,
				"p26a40": 75.9,
				"41a64": 1579,
				"p41a64": 75.8,
				"p65": 71.8
			},
			{
				"65": 163,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 2123,
				"pTotal": 23.9,
				"5a11": 436,
				"p5a11": 27.9,
				"12a25": 547,
				"p12a25": 20.4,
				"26a40": 473,
				"p26a40": 24.1,
				"41a64": 504,
				"p41a64": 24.2,
				"p65": 28.2
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"65": 62,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"Total": 4798,
				"pTotal": 54.1,
				"5a11": 515,
				"p5a11": 32.9,
				"12a25": 2139,
				"p12a25": 79.8,
				"26a40": 1330,
				"p26a40": 67.6,
				"41a64": 753,
				"p41a64": 36.1,
				"p65": 10.7
			},
			{
				"65": 515,
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"Respuesta": "No leyo",
				"Total": 4072,
				"pTotal": 45.9,
				"5a11": 1050,
				"p5a11": 67.1,
				"12a25": 540,
				"p12a25": 20.2,
				"26a40": 636,
				"p26a40": 32.4,
				"41a64": 1331,
				"p41a64": 63.9,
				"p65": 89.3
			}
		]
	}
}